doit.im 2014-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Best Online GTD Service for Getting Things Done, Always Online, Always With You!

## Privacy Policy

#### 1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

Doit.im collects personal information when you register with Doit.im, when you use Doit.im Services, when you visit Doit.im pages or the pages of certain Doit.im partners. Doit.im may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  
When you register we ask for information including your nick name and email address. When you register with Doit.im and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Doit.im automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address.  
Doit.im uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

#### 2\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

Doit.im does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. a. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Doit.im under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Doit.im communicate with you about offers from Doit.im. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  2. b. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  3. c. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Doit.im's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  4. d. We transfer information about you if Doit.im is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Doit.im will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### 3\. ACCOUNT INFORMATION EDITING

You can edit your Doit.im Account Information, at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Doit.im service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Doit.im Newsletter, that are considered part of your Doit.im account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

#### 4\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

#### 5\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Doit.im may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Doit.im account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

#### 6\. QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at contact@snoworange.com.
